ezyqatar.com 2017-06-06

# Business directory |Yellow pages | list of companies | free classifieds -Doha,Qatar

This is the privacy policy of ezyQatar and is applicable to all the people who intend to use any of our services.

In the course of registering and ordering from our company “ezyQatar” and availing its services mentioned on the website [www.ezyqatar.com](http://www.ezyqatar.com/), you (i.e. the User) may be asked to release personal information like name, job title, workplace address, e-mail address, date of birth, residence address, educational qualifications etc. This information is used to personalize your experience with us by fulfilling your requests for certain services, contacting you about our services and customizing the content that you see online on our website.

In order to prevent unauthorized sharing of your personal facts, we have suitable electronic and managerial processes in place. We are committed to protecting the confidentiality of all your personal information that you may share with us.

Your data, public or private would be used for market research, business development and strategic client analysis. If required, it may be shared with our advertisers who can call you for a query about a product or service that you are taking from us or other such business related reasons. It shall be deemed agreeable that you have given them the consent for this.

This policy, however, does not apply to the practices of organizations that we do not own or to people that we do not employ or manage.

Occasionally, at our discretion, your personal data may be released to the third parties who are working or acting on behalf of ezyQatar for furthering our business interests.

Advertisers are allowed to provide details about their products and trade on our website. This information can be viewed on the website by the general public and may not be screened by us, so whatever information the Advertisers post on the website will be at their own risk.

ezyQatar may transfer the content including your personal data to its database or share it with its trusted partners or government agencies whenever we believe it is appropriate, to comply with the law, protect your vital interest or fulfill requirements of administration process. This is done as a precautionary measure to maintain security and integrity of the website against legal liabilities, or in the event of merger and acquisition or a similar event.

Our customers or clients can post any relevant links on our site. These posts may carry link of third party sites too, but the third party sites can have independent privacy policies. We are not liable how they use or record personal data and therefore ezyQatar will not be accountable for the same.

Information collected through our website will be retained with us as long as we feel is necessary for our business or to ward off any legal or ethical issues.

By visiting ezyQatar and divulging your personal facts on the site, you acknowledge and give us your consent that your information, collected for reasons identified in our policy, can be transmitted to servers outside your resident jurisdiction. This is due to the global nature of business of our website. Users permit us to store information on servers located in different places and jurisdictions.

Users agree that they are releasing personal data on our website voluntarily to avail of our services. They are permitted to not disclose or withhold personal information too. However, if this practice hampers the completion of registration process, it is possible that the entire process of registration would be incomplete and deemed futile.

In cases where we have entered into a contract of confidentiality or non-disclosure with our corporate clients, this policy shall not affect that contract in any manner.

This Privacy Policy may be changed by ezyQatar periodically without notice so you will be responsible for checking these revisions. All amended terms will become effective upon our posting to the Website, and any use of the Website after such revisions have been posted will signify your consent to these changes.

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please send us an e-mail at [privacy@ezyqatar.com](mailto:privacy@ezyqatar.com)
